<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Taotao Kitchen</title>
    <link>https://taotao.kitchen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Taotao Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 17:05:43 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://taotao.kitchen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://taotao.kitchen/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 14:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taotao.kitchen/about/</guid>
      <description>滔, pronounced Tāo, means a massive wave of water. 饕, also pronounced Tāo, means a glutton. Together:
滔饕A big ass glutton, yes
 TaoTao brings Chinese food culture, knowledge, and history to the English speaking audience. TaoTao is your storytelling grandmother, a teacher passionate about passing down knowledge to his or her chef pupils, or simply your food-obsessed friend taking you out to his favourate hole-in-the-wall dumpling house.
Click here and go pig out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montreal Bagels</title>
      <link>https://taotao.kitchen/recipe/mtlbagel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 19:04:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://taotao.kitchen/recipe/mtlbagel/</guid>
      <description>If you hate reading stories, go to recipe here you filthy casual.
Read the Damn Intro Will Ya My roommate Alexis and I have always been hardcore fans of Montreal-style Bagels.
Alexis grew up in Bromont, which is just a little over an hour&amp;rsquo;s drive from Montreal. Lucky for him, he has had plenty of occasions indulging these sacred rings. My relationship with these bagels however, is somewhat different. Never having lived in Montreal (though I hope this will change soon), every occasion to lay my hands on these bagels was like striking gold on The Yukon Trail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
